in Hasanpur village located in Ber police station area of ​​capital Patna on Tuesday morning
when the body of
ICICI Lombard branch manager
Abhishek Varun was recovered along with his scooter from a farm well.
Abhishek was a resident of Kankarbagh
and was missing since Sunday night.  After this incident,
his family is in a bad condition and they are
considering it a murder conspiracy.
According to media reports, Abhishek had gone to a family function in
Ramakrishna Nagar with his wife and children on Sunday night.
His wife and children returned home around 10:00 pm.
But Abhishek stopped there.  His
wife told that he called at night and
said that he was returning home.  But at
3:00 in the night, Abhishek called again and told
that he had met with an accident.  After this
his phone started showing switched off.  The next day the
family started searching for him.  The
family members kept searching for him since morning from the place where the party was held to many hospitals.  But no
trace of him could be found.  After which the
family finally lodged a missing person FIR at Kankar Bagh police station.  A
police team also went to the party venue.  The police
also searched several hospitals adjacent to the bypass
and examined CCTV footage of the roads.
But no clue was
found.  It was about to be 24 hours.  But no
information could be found about Abhishek Varun.  His
phone being switched off after the news of the accident and his not
returning home was raising many questions.   The
family members were very worried.  they were scared.
He was continuously searched but no
information about him could be found.  Finally,
after about 24 hours, the police found Abhishek's body and his
scooter lying in a well near Ber Jail.
His slippers and scarf were also found from the incident site.  The
police is investigating this matter from every angle.
ASP Sadar and Phulwari
DSP Sushil Kumar said that the police have
found a CCTV footage in which Abhishek is
seen driving a scooter at 10:48 pm.
He was alone in the footage and it seemed as if someone was
following him.  In the footage, Abhishek was
seen in an intoxicated state.  At present the body has been
sent for post-mortem so that the
exact cause of death can be known.  Forensic teams
and dog squads are collecting evidence at the spot.
Police are investigating all possibilities including accident, suicide and murder.  There was
no railing around the well due to which there is a fear of an accident.
But after the family's
allegations of murder, the police are
also investigating the conspiracy angle.  Abhishek's
last mobile location was found in Bay area,
which is about 4 km from Ramakrishna Nagar.  It is far away.
The area is deserted, raising further questions in the investigation.
Abhishek's father
alleges that this is not a normal accident
but a murder committed under a conspiracy.
He says that someone forced Abhishek to make a
call and later murdered him.
How far?   It happened about the
last thing.
What?  Last happened that you must have had it at 3:00 on Sunday.
Which party have you come to here at 3:00 in the night?
Yes, I have come to a party here.
Where are these people's homes?
These people had a house in Darbhanga which was a hassle.
These people go and live in Kankar Bagh, we
live especially there.
What work did he do?  This is
considered to be their restaurant in the party,
when there was a party at night,
Babu did not send Supriya alone to her home, he
told her that there were medical shops there, so
they dropped her there,
after dropping her, he was talking to Supriya at night
and after that he went and said, okay, we have eaten and drank, so go to
sleep and send the child tomorrow morning.
Why did you call me at 45:30? I suddenly
woke up and woke up, so the
guest called you directly.  No no
Biya Biya yes
Supriya
yes they had told that then Papa some
incident happened, you and Ojha, some
for the elder son in law, those two men, please
reach there by 4:00, the police station told us to
come, don't say save me,
we have reached, the
police station called,
yes then after that we came and reached, from
where and when did you call, the
police station called, the same police station, who was at the police station,
called at
4 o'clock, that
means on the same night,
yes on the same night at quarter past one on
Sunday, the police station, you come, then we will go to that
area, search, where did the incident happen, is there a
little girl, what
incident happened, that is, what incident happened, this incident which has happened, who
knew this beforehand
that people are going here, went inside here,
where did they go for a walk, this was known beforehand, you must be
understanding that there was
a Sunday, Didi is
talking about yesterday morning, you are talking about yesterday morning, did
you tell anyone, was there any enmity
?
So this is called enmity,
this is an act of enmity.
This enmity has reduced, going on this route will
reduce the enmity.
Abhishek's mother-in-law has also made the same allegation and
said that he was given something to drink at the party
and then thrown into the well.  He
says that the people involved in the party
are responsible for this death.  There has been a
sensation in the area since the incident.  Is this just
an accident or murder?  After all,
how did Abhishek die?  Was he murdered and thrown into the well
?  The police is
busy finding answers to all such questions so that the
truth behind the mysterious death will soon be revealed.   That's all for
now in this report.  To
stay updated with such latest news of Bihar,
subscribe to our channel and
keep watching Sudarshan News Bihar.